Flying has shrunk the world!
飞行让世界变小了！
It's now possible to travel around the globe quickly and easily.
如今，快速便捷地环球旅行已成为可能。
Jumping on a plane and jetting off on holiday or a business trip is the norm for many of us, and with the rise of budget airlines, the number of people taking to the skies is increasing.
搭乘飞机外出度假或出差，对我们很多人来说已是常态。随着廉价航空公司的兴起，选择空中出行的人数也在不断增加。
But while air travel is costing us less, the cost to the environment is going up.
但尽管航空旅行的费用越来越低，其对环境破坏的代价却在不断上升。
Climate change is something we're all aware of now, and aviation companies know that some of the blame for this is being pointed at them.
气候变化已成为我们所有人都熟知的话题，航空公司也知道，人们正将部分责任归咎于它们。
Last year commercial airlines were forecasted to use about 97bn gallons of jet fuel.
去年，商业航空公司的航空燃油预计消耗量约为970亿加仑。
But while we could think twice about taking a flight in the first place, particularly a short-haul trip that could be made by train, technology might be the answer to reducing emissions and minimising the environmental damage.
不过，虽然我们一开始就可以慎重考虑是否要坐飞机（尤其是那些可以选择火车出行的短途旅程），但技术或许才是减少排放、将环境破坏降至最低的解决方案。
Recent developments have focussed on reducing the amount of fuel airliners burn.
近期的技术发展集中在减少客机的燃油消耗量上。
Making flying green and sustainable was the hot topic at the recent Dubai Air Show.
让飞行变得环保且可持续，是最近迪拜航空展的热门话题。
There was talk of advances in engine technology, making them more efficient, and possibly using biofuel to power aircraft.
会上讨论了发动机技术的进步（使其更高效），以及可能使用生物燃料为飞机提供动力。
Alejandro Rios Galvan, a bioenergy expert and professor at Khalifa University in Abu Dhabi, told the BBC that "these have the capacity to reduce the carbon footprint anywhere between 50-80% when you compare them to fossil (fuels)."
阿布扎比哈利法大学的生物能源专家、教授亚历杭德罗·里奥斯·加尔万向英国广播公司表示：“与化石燃料相比，这些生物燃料有能力将碳足迹减少50%至80%。”
And Phil Curnock, chief engineer of the civil future programme at Rolls-Royce, also suggested that electric hybrid engines could play a part for smaller aircraft, covering shorter distances.
劳斯莱斯民用未来项目的总工程师菲尔·柯诺克也提出，混合动力发动机可能适用于短途飞行的小型飞机。
He says "it offers the possibility of a carbon-neutral flight for a limited range."
他说：“这为有限航程内的碳中和飞行提供了可能。”
Being carbon neutral is the ultimate goal for the aviation industry, and one British airline, Easyjet, has recently said it would become the world's first major net zero carbon airline by offsetting carbon emissions.
碳中和是航空业的终极目标。英国易捷航空（Easyjet）最近表示，将通过抵消碳排放，成为全球首家大型净零碳航空公司。
Of course, aircraft manufacturers are constantly looking at ways to make their planes more fuel efficient.
当然，飞机制造商也在不断探索让飞机更省油的方法。
Boeing's Dreamliner, for example, is already in operation and uses 25 per cent less fuel per passenger compared with aircraft of a similar size.
例如，波音公司的梦想客机（Dreamliner）已投入运营，与同类尺寸的飞机相比，每位乘客的燃油消耗量减少了25%。
Other improvements include better aircraft aerodynamics, changes to ways aircraft taxi on runways, and the use of lighter materials.
其他改进措施还包括优化飞机的空气动力学设计、改变飞机在跑道上的滑行方式，以及使用更轻便的材料。
But if we can't kick the flying habit, it seems these are the developments we need to make in order to ensure air travel is as green as possible.
但如果我们无法戒除飞行的习惯，那么这些技术发展似乎是确保航空旅行尽可能环保所必需的。
But aviation experts agree it's going to take time.
不过航空专家一致认为，这需要时间。
We're left with short-term action such as taxing flights, regulation or protest - or being grounded and not flying at all.
目前我们可以采取的短期措施包括对航班征税、出台相关法规、发起抗议活动——或者干脆停飞，不再乘坐飞机。